(Penny:)Here's the difference.
(Penny:)The possibility exists
Leonard could have a birthday party...
(Penny:)...before hell freezes over.
(Howard:)Fine. If I do have a threesome,
you can't be part of it.
(Howard:)I'm just kidding. Yes, you can.
(Howard:)Can you bring a friend?
(Sheldon:)I think a birthday party is a terrible idea.
(Sheldon:)I envy Leonard for growing up
without that anguish.
(Penny:)Anguish?
(Sheldon:)Year after year,
I had to endure wearing conical hats...
(Sheldon:)...while being forced into the crowded,
sweaty hell of bouncy castles.
(Sheldon:)Not to mention being blindfolded...
(Sheldon:)...and spun toward
a grotesque tailless donkey...
(Sheldon:)...as the other children mocked
my disorientation.
(Penny:)Okay, sweetie, I understand you have scars
that no non-professional can heal...
...but nevertheless, we're gonna
throw Leonard a birthday party.
I'm extremely uncomfortable
with dancing...
(Sheldon:)...loud music and most other forms
of alcohol-induced frivolity.
(Penny:)- Nevertheless...
- In addition...